Guide to the West Coast Punk and New Wave Club flyers, ca 1979-1982.
West Coast Punk and New Wave Club flyers,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
West Coast Punk and New Wave Club flyers, ca 1979-1982.
8129
1 cubic foot.
Fliers and posters.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
This collection from a West Coast club promoter offers a glimpse of punk and new wave influenced music, art, film, and underground culture in the San Francisco Bay Area in the late 1970s and early 1980s.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
This collection from a West Coast club promoter offers a glimpse of punk and new wave influenced music, art, film, and underground culture in the San Francisco Bay Area in the late 1970s and early 1980s. Approximately 333 flyers, handbills and posters advertising punk and new wave music and art shows and events in Berkeley, San Francisco, Oakland, and other California Bay Area venues. Bands represented include The Dead Kennedys, D.O.A., The Nuns, The Dils, The Misfits, The Avengers, Iggy Pop,; events represented include "Rock Against Racism 1980", "End Barrio Warfare!", and "Rock Against Reagan."
SUBJECTS
Subjects:
Advertising.; Advertising fliers.; Art and society.; Avant-garde (Aesthetics).; Commercial art.; Counterculture.; Graphic arts.; Intellectual life.; Music -- Political aspects.; New wave music.; Popular culture.; Posters.; Punk culture.; Punk culture and art.; Punk rock music.; Punk rock musicians.; Subculture.; Subversive activities.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Fliers and posters
CONTAINER LIST
- Fliers and posters, 1978-1989
  - Pop Steady: The Famous Titans, 1976-02-26-1981-02-26; Illustrated with drawing of the band (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At Ashkenaz
  - Plutonium Players: Reagan for Shah, 1975-12-03-1980-12-07; Illustrated with a photograph of Virginia Cholesterol (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At Hotel Utah and Mission Blue Caf
  - Roots Rock Reggae, 1976-01-31-1981-01-31; Illustrated with a drawing of a palm tree; blue stock (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At Savoy Tivoli
  - Middle Class!, 1976-1981; Illustrated with a drawing of a man’s face; pink stock (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At Sound of Music
  - Earl Zero and Cornerstone Wild Remain, Undated; Illustration of man (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At Back D.O.R.
  - KPFA 94 FM, Undated; Illustrated with photographs of Kennedy and Reagan (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At Maximum Rock and Roll
  - 13 Code of Honor Lewd, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At Tool and Die
  - Deprogrammers, Undertakers, 1980; Illustrated with map of venue and American flag; orange stock (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At Vex
  - Bill Graham, Live in Person, 1981-05-12; Illustrated with a drawing of an octopus (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At Maximum Rock ’N’Roll
  - Suburban Lawns Guns Club, Undated; Illustrated with architectural drawings (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At Jett’s, July 12
  - Guerrilla Disco Riot, 1981-06-16; Illustrated with a photo collage (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At Top Floor Gallery
  - The Enemy, 1980-07-24; Illustrated with a drawing of a laughing man; printed in red and black (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Lip Service, 1980-05-31; Illustrated with a small drawing of lips; one color; small chip to upper left corner; browned (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At Club 88
  - In the Woods, Undated; Illustrated with photo collage (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At Cameo Theatre, July-August
  - So Squeezably Soft, It’s Irresistible!, Undated; Illustrated with a drawing of Capitol Hill depicted in $100 dollar bills (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - “Here’s the tough but gentle war you need”…says Arthur Godfrey, Undated; Illustrated with a photo collage (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Arenal, Undated; Illustrated with a photo collage (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Some Faith Show: For the Suffering, 1981-03-14; Illustrated with photographs (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At S.O.M. Club
  - Wanderlust With Friends Brevity Phantom Limbs, 1982-01-27; Illustrated with geometric designs (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At Mabuhay Gardens
  - Group Rockola, 1980-11-13; Illustrated with photograph of school children (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Studio
  - Poetry Series, 1980; Illustrated with abstract design and photograph of woman; yellow stock (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At San Francisco Art Institute
  - Untitled Poster, Undated; Illustrated with umbrella, arrows, glass, and man (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, Undated; Illustrated with photo collage; pink stock (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Beat the Clock: Take the New Year! Dance party for RW, Undated; Illustrated with photo collage featuring clock (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At Sportsman’s Lodge, December 31
  - Meeting Adjourned, Undated; Illustrated with board room onlooking a public hanging (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Progress, Undated; Illustrated with photo collage featuring workers destroying luxury items (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, Undated; Illustrated with photo collage featuring a man with fire and a gun on his dinner plate (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Paintings: Fredenthal, Young, Mulder, Undated; Illustrated with photographs of artists (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At A R E Market, August 4-15
  - Impostors, VIPS, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At Rose and Thistle, March 5
  - Bucks, 1980-03-05; Illustrated with photo collage featuring photograph of band and dollar bills (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - T.V. O. D.? Try the New Maximum Rock ’N Roll, Undated; Illustrated with photo collage of men shooting a television; yellow stock (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At Maximum Rock ’N’ Roll
  - Brain Rust. Misfits in a Jungle of Buildings, 1985-06-28; Illustrated with photo collage of child dressed in native garb (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At Club Foot
  - Gnat Music with the Moot Choir Plus Target Video, 1979-02-22; Illustrated with two men playing with a ball (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At Victoria Theatre
  - Wild Women of Borneo Arkansas Man G.O.D. Benefit, Undated; Illustrated with photo collage featuring headless barbie and television screens (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At Hotel Utah, March 5
  - The I-Bean. The Contractions/Silvertone, The DFFS, The Lloyds, Undated; Illustrated with small image of knife stabbing piece of paper (Box 1, Folder 1)
    August 9, 11, and 18
  - Zeros Wall of Voodoo, Contractions, 1979-09-21-1984-09-21; Illustrated with photographs of men (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At Deaf Club
  - Los Microwaves. See Spot Baby Buddha., Undated; Illustrated with photograph of woman and female mask (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At Fad Mab, April 1
  - The Patriot, Undated; Illustrated with manipulated photograph of man with American flag (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Mr. E’s New Humans, Undated; Illustrated text; full color (Box 1, Folder 1)
    “Mr. E is the most controversial artist since WARHOL, and NEW HUMANS may be the Art show of the decade…” At Goodman Building, September 5
  - Zeros, Undated; Illustrated with photo collage of protesters and fireworks; yellow stock; one color (Box 1, Folder 1)
    July 4th
  - The Urge, The Zeros, 1979-04-08-1984-04-08; Illustrated with photographs of the bands; printed on blue stock (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At Stockton Market
  - Who Controls the Button? A: An individual e.g. Jimmy Ronnie or possibly Johnny; B: human nature e.g.; C: technology; D: Capitalism, Undated; Illustrated with photograph of a woman appearing to have a headache (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Piglatin: Whitefronts, 1980-04-13-1986-04-13; Illustrated with bugs (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, Undated; Illustrated with a bald eagle pierced with a safety pin (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Les Nickelettes Contractions, Jim Turner, The Baltimores, Sisters of Perpetual Indulgence, Les Nickelettes 10th Anniversary Bash, 1982-04-10; Illustrated with photographs of the band; pink stock (Box 1, Folder 1)
    At Capp Street Center
  - America Help! Sometimes you just know when something terrible is about to happen…Minor Threat, 1982-06-25; Illustrated with a photograph of the Statue of Liberty with a face mask (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, Undated; Illustrated with photo collage featuring Jesus on a cross of dollar bills entitled “Idol" (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - CY3, Undated; Illustrated with a photo collage featuring men’s heads, skeletons, and a crying baby (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Avengers, D. O. A., Nubs, Undated; Illustrated with drawing of lion (Box 1, Folder 2)
    At NT Cafe, April 14
  - Images From South Africa. An International Art Show. Opening Reception, 1980-04-18-1986-04-18; Illustrated with a drawing of a tiger; printed on blue stock (Box 1, Folder 2)
    At Media
  - The Hot Line, Undated; Illustrated with photograph of telephone booth and factory (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Incite!, Undated; Image of Roman Coliseum against columns of stock prices (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bonds of Savagery, Undated; Collage of military imagery a ballet dancer, and fragments of a musical score (lyrics: “how do you get the truth through?”) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Out of Control, Undated; Illustrated with photograph of control room; one color (Box 1, Folder 2)
    At Shoreham Control Room
  - Wolva Rines. Wolverines are playing, 1980-09-15-1986-09-19; Illustrated with photograph of woman (Box 1, Folder 2)
    At Rat’s Place, September 15 and 19
  - A Look at What’s Ahead: The Reagan Future. Pattern of things to come, Undated; Illustrated as front page of newspaper (Box 1, Folder 2)
    San Francisco “Chronimer."
  - 2nd Annual Postcard Palace Mail-In Postcard Art Show, Undated; Illustrated with postcards (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Send entries by Feb 5, original artwork, no limit—no return. At B.W.D.B
  - Bertrano or Hats Don’t Lie, Undated; Illustrated with drawing of man behind bars (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Pacific Repertory Company. At Cameo Theatre, June 27-29, July 5-26, and August 3
  - Malatesta: A film by Peter Lilienthal. Plus Pacific St. Films, Red Squad, 1982-05-22; Illustrated with photograph of Errico Malatesta; printed on red stock; one color (Box 1, Folder 2)
    At A.R.E. Gallery
  - How Many Capitalists in Your City Don’t Want You to Do This?, Undated; Illustrated with photograph of someone burning a selective service form (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Capitalists would like you to go on thinking there’s “nothing you can do to stop them” because when people start doing something the results are inspiring
  - Don’t Register. It’s your life! The draft=war, Undated; Illustrated with war planes (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Untitled, Undated; Illustrated with photograph of Adolf Eichmann with “SHELL” markings (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Stop the Buildup, Undated; Illustrated with collage of words such as “war” and “warning (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Desire Films Presents: Baltimore Independent Cinema, 1980-12-14; Illustrated with possible film still (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Pro-Life, Undated; Photograph of two woman and a military man at a cemetery (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Tomorrow Belongs to Me, Undated; Illustrated with photo collage of little girls watching destruction (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Maximum Rock ’N’ Roll is Moving to 8-10p.m. Tue. Starting June 12., 1979-06-12-1984-06-12; Illustrated with photo collage of lobster driving a convertible car (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Beware! These are permanent labels. Danger! Perasticky!!!, 1980; Sheet of large stickersIllustrated with well-known artworks (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bonds of Savagery, Undated; Collage of military imagery a ballet dancer, and fragments of a musical score (lyrics: “How do you get the truth through?”) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Elvis Presley Memorial Art Show by Bob Basile, 1979; Illustrated with photograph of Presley with gun; printed on beige stock (Box 1, Folder 2)
    At The Black Room
  - Canyon Sam Tede Matthews Poets, 1981-03-04; Illustrated with photographs of poets (Box 1, Folder 2)
    At Cafe Stand
  - Death…Or Life? Create Your Life Not Destroy It, Undated; Illustrated with a photo collage by Eva Lake (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ruin, N. (The Act of Destruction)—Syn. Extinction, Demolition, Overthrow, Undated; Illustrated with a photograph of Capitol Hill in ruins (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Wargasm!, 1980; Illustrated with a drawing of a nuclear family at the dinner table (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Miss America, Undated; Illustrated with photographs of Miss America pageant participants (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Rock Against Thatcher, Undated; Illustrated with a photograph of Margaret Thatcher and text (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Rotten, Undated; Illustrated with an American flag decorated with teeth (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - These Are Your Greatest Treasures!, 1980; Illustrated with a photograph of a man coming out of a large safe (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - No Reason to Live? Don’t give up! Don’t forget your dog! Anti-peace radicals. The Fear of atomic extinction., 1979; Illustrated with a photo collage of American luxuries (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Ruling Class, 1982; Illustrated with a photo collage by Winston Smith featuring Reagan jumping a horse over a crowd of people (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Specimen, 1980; Illustrated with a photo collage by Winston Smith featuring scientists (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Coming Is Brother Big, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - One Man’s Profit is Another Man’s Poison! Are you just a statistic?, Undated; Illustrated with a photo collage featuring radiation imagery (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - End Barrio Warfare! Educate Raza!, 1980-03-01; Illustrated with a photo collage featuring a skeleton in a car (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Destroy What Destroys You! Build Revolutionary Guerrilla Cells!, Undated; Illustrated with a photograph of a man shooting a gun (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Untitled, 1980; Illustrated with a photo collage of people watching an atomic bomb explode (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - If You Send Your Children Away, Undated; Illustrated with photo collage of soldiers (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Come On Baby Take A Chance With Us, Undated; Illustrated with a photo collage of soldiers and barracks (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The killer awoke before dawn he put his books on he took a face from the ancient gallery…, Undated; Illustrated with text and a geometric collager (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Mo-ther, Undated; Illustrated with a photo collage of soldiers (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - This Is the End, Undated; Illustrate with a photo collage of men on horses (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Artists End?, Undated; Illustrate with a drawing of a man; full color (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Untitled, Undated; Print of a skeleton and a globe (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alarm, Undated; Illustrated with drawing of a hand (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Iggy Pop Plus MiSex, 1980-04-06-1986-04-06; Illustrated with a photograph of Iggy Pop; orange stock (Box 1, Folder 3)
    At Pauley Ballroom UC Berkeley
  - Contractions, SVT, Pushups, 1980-01-25-1986-01-25; Illustrated with a drawing of aliens and camels; orange stock (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Wounds, Angst, Paris, Working, 1982-04-23; Illustrated with a photograph by Chester Simpson (Box 1, Folder 3)
    At On Broadway Theatre Nightclub
  - Mindsweeper, 1980-09-03-1980-09-05; Illustrated with a photo collage (Box 1, Folder 3)
    At Palms
  - Hey! Stop dropping that plutonium around here!, Undated; Illustrated with a photograph by Sue Fishben; printed in red and black (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Toiling Midgets / Lifers / Matchheads. Don’t say a word., 1981-11-19; Illustrated with a drawing by K. Seltzer of a man with a gun to his head; green stock (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Catch the Varve Twice on March 4th!, Undated; Illustrated with a photograph of a woman sitting on a couch and a man jumping (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Mutants?, Undated; Illustrated with a photograph of four Chihuahuas (Box 1, Folder 3)
    At Mabuhay
  - The Lewd and Special Guest S and M, plus Revenge, Illustrated with a drawing of a vampire (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Indoor Life, 1980-04-03; Illustrated with a drawing of a man running; blue stock (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - R and N2. Vaudeo: Tales of life and death from the electronic battleground of sound and vision!, 1980-09-05-1980-09-13; Illustrated with a photo collage by Dob Jeremy in the form of a person drinking water; printed in blue and black (Box 1, Folder 3)
    September 5-6, 12-13, 1980
  - VauxHall Mab Noel (Box 1, Folder 3)
    At Vauxhall
  - Rocker, Deathwatch and The Romulans, Featuring Spencer Dryden, 1982-06-15; Illustrated with a scull and bones (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Crop on the Waterfront. Also: Romeo Void, 1980-03-21; Illustrated with photographs of men (Box 1, Folder 3)
    At Mission Rock Resort
  - Enter the World of the Deaf for Just 5 Minutes, Undated; Illustrated with a photo collage featuring Marilyn Monroe (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Barry Bean, The Stone Rayons. No cover!, 1982-02-25; Illustrated with a drawing of a boy; one color (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - KPFA Radio Maximum Rock ’N’ Roll with Tim and Ray. Out! Chris Lowry. Johnnie Walker Show. No More, Undated; Illustrated with a photo collage featuring people listening to the radio (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Avengers Plus Zeros April 27, Undated; Illustrated with a photo collage of comic book illustrations (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Neon Clone and Neon Clone and The Manipulators, 1980-01-06-1985-01-06; Illustrated with photographs of band members (Box 1, Folder 3)
    At Intersection
  - The Stigmas. Easter Dance, 1979; Illustrated with a surrealist drawing (Box 1, Folder 3)
    At Temple Beautiful
  - Also: Tom Eliot, Solo Bass Perform. Life by Mail, appearing Friday, 1980-06-20; Illustrated with a photograph of a man looking at his hands (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Aiming to Hit: No Alternative, 1980-01-20; Illustrated with war symbols; orange stock; one color (Box 1, Folder 3)
    At Oil Can Harry’s Marathon Ballroom
  - Meet Ras Michael!, 1980-01-10; Illustrated with a photo collage of Ras Muchael and the Sons of Negus; pink stock (Box 1, Folder 3)
    At Leopold Record
  - Desiring Machines: Art Performances., Undated; Illustrated with a photograph of a man and woman in bed; small closed tears to right edge (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Dominic Perret, Judy Bell, Genevieve Boutet de Monvel, Punch and Banger, Animal Things, Morgan Garood, Eric Garrick, Susan Wood, Ellen Ster, Dog (of LongShormen), Lynndel, Robert Hyatt. All shows begin at 9pm. At Club Foot, June 12, 19, 26, July 3 and 17
  - VIPs, 1980-03-01-1980-03-26; Illustrated with a photo collage by Peter Soe, Jr. featuring a photograph of the band (Box 1, Folder 3)
    March: Sat. 1 Roosevelt’s, Tue. 4 Berkeley Sq, Wed. 5 Roses and Thistle, Fri. 21 Back D.O.R., Sat. 22 Berkeley Sq., Wed. 26 Back D.O.R.
  - MJB 23 Screams. Sacripolitical Pukes, Undated; Illustrated with a photo collage featuring the surface of the moon and a man looking through a window (Box 1, Folder 3)
    At Club Foot, May 31
  - Destroy a Country. Defy Mediocrity. The Feederz, Undated; Illustrated with instructions for making a molotov cocktail (Box 1, Folder 3)
    At Mabury and Rock City, October 22-24
  - The Conservatives, 1980-11-07-1980-11-09; Illustrated with a photograph of a man reading; orange stock (Box 1, Folder 3)
    At Le Disque and Mabuhay Gardens
  - Wanted!? Apprehendable at your local card store. Miss Dish, 1980; Illustrated with a photograph of a woman smoking a cigarette (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - No More Power to War Plants…, Undated; Illustrated with photographs of electricity plants (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - X Brain Fry. 3 Alighed Aldocroft photo-film-fluid audio response. Kaleidoscope projectors and experimental/New Wave, 1980-07 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Meanwhile, Back in the U.S.A. Rock Against Reagan, Illustrated with a drawing of skull and guitar, attributed to “Mike" (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Mark and Marty present Real Television. Channel 25. Fridays 7:30. Tuesdays 9:00, Undated; Illustrated with a photograph of a man on television (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Barry Beam Listings, Undated; Illustrated with a photo collage featuring a man in a suit with a comically small head (Box 1, Folder 3)
    At Back D.O.R., July 5
  - Radio On. A feature film in black and white with music from David Bowie, Kraftwerk, Robert Fripp and Stiff Records (Ian Dury, Lene Lovich, Wreckless Eric, Devo), 1980; Illustrated with a film still featuring a plane flying over a car (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Exclusive Bay Area Showings. A BFI-Road Movies Production in association
  - Rock and Roll! Everybody Comes to Hear. The Next Exit Band, 1979-06-02-1984-06-02; Illustrated with photographs of celebrities and the Mona Lisa (Box 1, Folder 3)
    At International Caf
  - Los Microwaves. Ex-Avengers guitarist Craig Westermark new group, Rondos, 1979-06-07-1984-06-07; Illustrated with a photo collage featuring a chef and vinyl records (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Panjandrum Saturday Night Poetry, 1981-01-24; Illustrated with a surrealist drawing of four buildings; light blue stock (Box 1, Folder 3)
    At Panjandrum Books
  - Minimal Man on Broadway. Code of Honor and German Shepherds, 1982-04-03; Illustrated with a photograph of man (Box 1, Folder 3)
    At Theatre Nightclub
  - Gange of Four Plus Guests, 1980-05-22 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    At American Indian Center
  - Wild Nixon With Guest Vocalist Ricky Williams. Play: a benefit for underground bands, 1981-03-05; Illustrated with a french newspaper page (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - New Years Eve Blow Out. Minors welcome. Impatient Youth, PLUGZ, Black Flag. No Alternative. Two Tone. Toiling Midgets, 1980-12-31; Illustrated with a photo collage featuring “president-elect reagan reveals Republican posture on defense”; pink stock (Box 1, Folder 3)
    At RRZ
  - Appliances, Henry Kaiser, Philip-Dmitri Galas, Name, Eduardo., Undated; Illustrated with various school yearbook photographs (Box 1, Folder 3)
    At Club Foot Club, June 21
  - Gardner’s Pick of the Crop. Dance theatre performance, Undated; Illustrated with three photographs of gardeners (Box 1, Folder 4)
    At Academy West dance Center, July 12-13
  - Cha-Cha-Billy, Push-Ups, Undated; Illustrated with an abstract design featuring symbols of music and dancing (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - At the End of Their Rope…Ku Klux Klones, Illustrated with a photo collage featuring a pyramid of frogs (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - No Gang of Four Issue, Undated; Two leaves;Illustrated with a photo collage featuring a drawing entitled, “Sid Sings ‘My-Way,’” and a musical score (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Help—I’m Under Japanese Influence!, Undated; Drawing of two stick figures, Japanese flag, mushroom cloud and jumbo jet (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Hey Kids! Become human skeletons!, 1980; Illustrated with a photo collage featuring a poem and various photograph of people (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Rock Against Racism, 1980; Illustrated with photograph of Nazis an a short note of thanks from Rock Against Racism (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Thought Form for August 12. 1,030 persons are involved, 1980-08-12; Illustrated with geometric drawings (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Outside Agitators. Plus idiot child The Fukkups and Peer Pressure, 1981; Illustrated with a drawing of two woman smiling at a Klu Klux Klan cross burning (Box 1, Folder 4)
    At Nico’s Underground
  - Future Theatre, Undated; Illustrated with checkered background (Box 1, Folder 4)
    The most provocative, puzzling, and prolific group in new concept performance of this generation
  - Feast Your Eyes on This, My Love, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Ah yes! Roast midget sautéed in butter. A rare delicacy ever since the midget shortage they’ve been hard to come by. But now that Reagan’s in office… Illustrated with a photo collage of a couple cooking a little person.
  - Alterboys INTL. Studios in Conjunction w/ Subterranean Reco Rds Is Please to Announce a Forthcoming 12" Vinyl, Undated; Illustrated with a photograph of a man in a suit (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Retro Films, 1980-09-19; Illustrated with a drawing of three falling cubes (Box 1, Folder 4)
    At Valencia Tool and Die
  - Longshormen, Dog Town, Oblong Rhondes, Myke Reilly, Undated; Illustrated with three photographs: trash, women in the back of a pickup truck,and a coffee truck (Box 1, Folder 4)
    At Club Foot, March 20